<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<doxygen xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="compound.xsd" version="1.8.16">
  <compounddef id="namespacePHPMailer" kind="namespace" language="PHP">
    <compoundname>PHPMailer</compoundname>
    <briefdescription>
    </briefdescription>
    <detaileddescription>
<para><ref refid="classPHPMailer" kindref="compound">PHPMailer</ref> - PHP email creation and transport class. PHP Version 5</para>
<para><ref refid="" kindref="compound">The PHPMailer GitHub project  Marcus Bointon (Synchro/coolbru) <ulink url="mailto:phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk">phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk</ulink>  Jim Jagielski (jimjag) <ulink url="mailto:jimjag@gmail.com">jimjag@gmail.com</ulink>  Andy Prevost (codeworxtech) <ulink url="mailto:codeworxtech@users.sourceforge.net">codeworxtech@users.sourceforge.net</ulink>  Brent R. Matzelle (original founder)  2012 - 2014 Marcus Bointon  2010 - 2012 Jim Jagielski  2004 - 2009 Andy Prevost  <ulink url="http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/lesser.html">http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/lesser.html</ulink> GNU Lesser General Public License  This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful - WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. PHPMailer - PHP email creation and transport class.  Marcus Bointon (Synchro/coolbru) <ulink url="mailto:phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk">phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk</ulink>  Jim Jagielski (jimjag) <ulink url="mailto:jimjag@gmail.com">jimjag@gmail.com</ulink>  Andy Prevost (codeworxtech) <ulink url="mailto:codeworxtech@users.sourceforge.net">codeworxtech@users.sourceforge.net</ulink>  Brent R. Matzelle (original founder) PHPMailer exception handler PHPMailer - PHP email creation and transport class. PHP Version 5.4  <ulink url="https://github.com/PHPMailer/PHPMailer/">https://github.com/PHPMailer/PHPMailer/</ulink> The PHPMailer GitHub project  Marcus Bointon (Synchro/coolbru) <ulink url="mailto:phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk">phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk</ulink>  Jim Jagielski (jimjag) <ulink url="mailto:jimjag@gmail.com">jimjag@gmail.com</ulink>  Andy Prevost (codeworxtech) <ulink url="mailto:codeworxtech@users.sourceforge.net">codeworxtech@users.sourceforge.net</ulink>  Brent R. Matzelle (original founder)  2012 - 2014 Marcus Bointon  2010 - 2012 Jim Jagielski  2004 - 2009 Andy Prevost  <ulink url="http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/lesser.html">http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/lesser.html</ulink> GNU Lesser General Public License  This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful - WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. PHPMailerOAuth - PHPMailer subclass adding OAuth support.    Marcus Bointon () <ulink url="mailto:phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk">phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk</ulink> PHPMailerOAuthGoogle - Wrapper for League OAuth2 Google provider.    Marcus Bointon () <ulink url="mailto:phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk">phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk</ulink>  <ulink url="https://github.com/thephpleague/oauth2-client">https://github.com/thephpleague/oauth2-client</ulink> PHPMailer POP-Before-SMTP Authentication Class. PHP Version 5  <ulink url="https://github.com/PHPMailer/PHPMailer/">https://github.com/PHPMailer/PHPMailer/</ulink>  Marcus Bointon (Synchro/coolbru) <ulink url="mailto:phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk">phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk</ulink>  Jim Jagielski (jimjag) <ulink url="mailto:jimjag@gmail.com">jimjag@gmail.com</ulink>  Andy Prevost (codeworxtech) <ulink url="mailto:codeworxtech@users.sourceforge.net">codeworxtech@users.sourceforge.net</ulink>  Brent R. Matzelle (original founder)  2012 - 2014 Marcus Bointon  2010 - 2012 Jim Jagielski  2004 - 2009 Andy Prevost  <ulink url="http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/lesser.html">http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/lesser.html</ulink> GNU Lesser General Public License  This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful - WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. PHPMailer POP-Before-SMTP Authentication Class. Specifically for PHPMailer to use for RFC1939 POP-before-SMTP authentication. Does not support APOP.  Richard Davey (original author) <ulink url="mailto:rich@corephp.co.uk">rich@corephp.co.uk</ulink>  Marcus Bointon (Synchro/coolbru) <ulink url="mailto:phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk">phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk</ulink>  Jim Jagielski (jimjag) <ulink url="mailto:jimjag@gmail.com">jimjag@gmail.com</ulink>  Andy Prevost (codeworxtech) <ulink url="mailto:codeworxtech@users.sourceforge.net">codeworxtech@users.sourceforge.net</ulink> PHPMailer RFC821 SMTP email transport class. PHP Version 5  <ulink url="https://github.com/PHPMailer/PHPMailer/">https://github.com/PHPMailer/PHPMailer/</ulink> The PHPMailer GitHub project  Marcus Bointon (Synchro/coolbru) <ulink url="mailto:phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk">phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk</ulink>  Jim Jagielski (jimjag) <ulink url="mailto:jimjag@gmail.com">jimjag@gmail.com</ulink>  Andy Prevost (codeworxtech) <ulink url="mailto:codeworxtech@users.sourceforge.net">codeworxtech@users.sourceforge.net</ulink>  Brent R. Matzelle (original founder)  2014 Marcus Bointon  2010 - 2012 Jim Jagielski  2004 - 2009 Andy Prevost  <ulink url="http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/lesser.html">http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/lesser.html</ulink> GNU Lesser General Public License  This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful - WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. PHPMailer RFC821 SMTP email transport class. Implements RFC 821 SMTP commands and provides some utility methods for sending mail to an SMTP server.  Chris Ryan  Marcus Bointon <ulink url="mailto:phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk">phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk</ulink> Armenian PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Hrayr Grigoryan <ulink url="mailto:hrayr@bits.am">hrayr@bits.am</ulink> Arabic PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  bahjat al mostafa <ulink url="mailto:bahjat983@hotmail.com">bahjat983@hotmail.com</ulink> Azerbaijani PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list   Bosnian PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Ermin Islamagić <ulink url="mailto:ermin@islamagic.com">ermin@islamagic.com</ulink> Belarusian PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Aleksander Maksymiuk <ulink url="mailto:info@setpro.pl">info@setpro.pl</ulink> Bulgarian PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Mikhail Kyosev <ulink url="mailto:mialygk@gmail.com">mialygk@gmail.com</ulink> Catalan PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Ivan </ref></para>
<para>Chinese <ref refid="classPHPMailer" kindref="compound">PHPMailer</ref> language file: refer to English translation for definitive list</para>
<para><simplesect kind="author"><para>LiuXin <ulink url="http://www.80x86.cn/blog/">http://www.80x86.cn/blog/</ulink></para>
</simplesect>
Czech <ref refid="classPHPMailer" kindref="compound">PHPMailer</ref> language file: refer to English translation for definitive list</para>
<para>Danish <ref refid="classPHPMailer" kindref="compound">PHPMailer</ref> language file: refer to English translation for definitive list</para>
<para><simplesect kind="author"><para>Mikael Stokkebro <ulink url="mailto:info@stokkebro.dk">info@stokkebro.dk</ulink></para>
</simplesect>
German <ref refid="classPHPMailer" kindref="compound">PHPMailer</ref> language file: refer to English translation for definitive list</para>
<para>Greek <ref refid="classPHPMailer" kindref="compound">PHPMailer</ref> language file: refer to English translation for definitive list</para>
<para>Esperanto <ref refid="classPHPMailer" kindref="compound">PHPMailer</ref> language file: refer to English translation for definitive list</para>
<para>Spanish <ref refid="classPHPMailer" kindref="compound">PHPMailer</ref> language file: refer to English translation for definitive list</para>
<para><simplesect kind="author"><para>Matt Sturdy <ulink url="mailto:matt.sturdy@gmail.com">matt.sturdy@gmail.com</ulink></para>
</simplesect>
Estonian <ref refid="classPHPMailer" kindref="compound">PHPMailer</ref> language file: refer to English translation for definitive list</para>
<para><simplesect kind="author"><para>Indrek Päri </para>
</simplesect>
<simplesect kind="author"><para>Elan Ruusamäe <ulink url="mailto:glen@delfi.ee">glen@delfi.ee</ulink></para>
</simplesect>
Persian/Farsi <ref refid="classPHPMailer" kindref="compound">PHPMailer</ref> language file: refer to English translation for definitive list</para>
<para><simplesect kind="author"><para>Ali Jazayeri <ulink url="mailto:jaza.ali@gmail.com">jaza.ali@gmail.com</ulink> </para>
</simplesect>
<simplesect kind="author"><para>Mohammad Hossein Mojtahedi <ulink url="mailto:mhm5000@gmail.com">mhm5000@gmail.com</ulink></para>
</simplesect>
Finnish <ref refid="classPHPMailer" kindref="compound">PHPMailer</ref> language file: refer to English translation for definitive list</para>
<para><simplesect kind="author"><para>Jyry Kuukanen</para>
</simplesect>
Faroese <ref refid="classPHPMailer" kindref="compound">PHPMailer</ref> language file: refer to English translation for definitive list</para>
<para><simplesect kind="author"><para>Dávur Sørensen <ulink url="http://www.profo-webdesign.dk">http://www.profo-webdesign.dk</ulink></para>
</simplesect>
French <ref refid="classPHPMailer" kindref="compound">PHPMailer</ref> language file: refer to English translation for definitive list</para>
<para>Some French punctuation requires a thin non-breaking space (U+202F) character before it, for example before a colon or exclamation mark. There is one of these characters between these quotes: &quot; &quot; <ref refid="" kindref="compound">Galician PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  by Donato Rouco <ulink url="mailto:donatorouco@gmail.com">donatorouco@gmail.com</ulink> Hebrew PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Ronny Sherer <ulink url="mailto:ronny@hoojima.com">ronny@hoojima.com</ulink> Croatian PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Hrvoj3e <ulink url="mailto:hrvoj3e@gmail.com">hrvoj3e@gmail.com</ulink> Hungarian PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  -75 Indonesian PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Cecep Prawiro <ulink url="mailto:cecep.prawiro@gmail.com">cecep.prawiro@gmail.com</ulink> Italian PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Ilias Bartolini <ulink url="mailto:brain79@inwind.it">brain79@inwind.it</ulink>  Stefano Sabatini <ulink url="mailto:sabas88@gmail.com">sabas88@gmail.com</ulink> Japanese PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Mitsuhiro Yoshida <ulink url="http://mitstek.com/">http://mitstek.com/</ulink>  Yoshi Sakai <ulink url="http://bluemooninc.jp/">http://bluemooninc.jp/</ulink> Georgian PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Avtandil Kikabidze aka LONGMAN <ulink url="mailto:akalongman@gmail.com">akalongman@gmail.com</ulink> Korean PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  ChalkPE <ulink url="mailto:amato0617@gmail.com">amato0617@gmail.com</ulink> Lithuanian PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Dainius Kaupaitis <ulink url="mailto:dk@sum.lt">dk@sum.lt</ulink> Latvian PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Eduards M. <ulink url="mailto:e@npd.lv">e@npd.lv</ulink> Malaysian PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Nawawi Jamili <ulink url="mailto:nawawi@rutweb.com">nawawi@rutweb.com</ulink> Norwegian Bokmål PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list Dutch PHPMailer language file: refer to class.phpmailer.php for definitive list.  Tuxion <ulink url="mailto:team@tuxion.nl">team@tuxion.nl</ulink> Polish PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list Portuguese (European) PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Jonadabe <ulink url="mailto:jonadabe@hotmail.com">jonadabe@hotmail.com</ulink> Brazilian Portuguese PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Paulo Henrique Garcia <ulink url="mailto:paulo@controllerweb.com.br">paulo@controllerweb.com.br</ulink>  Lucas Guimarães <ulink url="mailto:lucas@lucasguimaraes.com">lucas@lucasguimaraes.com</ulink>  Phelipe Alves <ulink url="mailto:phelipealvesdesouza@gmail.com">phelipealvesdesouza@gmail.com</ulink>  Fabio Beneditto <ulink url="mailto:fabiobeneditto@gmail.com">fabiobeneditto@gmail.com</ulink> Romanian PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Alex Florea <ulink url="mailto:alecz.fia@gmail.com">alecz.fia@gmail.com</ulink> Serbian PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Александар Јевремовић <ulink url="mailto:ajevremovic@gmail.com">ajevremovic@gmail.com</ulink> Russian PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Alexey Chumakov <ulink url="mailto:alex@chumakov.ru">alex@chumakov.ru</ulink>  Foster Snowhill <ulink url="mailto:i18n@forstwoof.ru">i18n@forstwoof.ru</ulink> Slovak PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Michal Tinka <ulink url="mailto:michaltinka@gmail.com">michaltinka@gmail.com</ulink> Slovene PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Klemen Tušar <ulink url="mailto:techouse@gmail.com">techouse@gmail.com</ulink> Swedish PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Johan Linnér <ulink url="mailto:johan@linner.biz">johan@linner.biz</ulink> Turkish PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Elçin Özel  Can Yılmaz  Mehmet Benlioğlu    Ogün Karakuş Ukrainian PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  Yuriy Rudyy <ulink url="mailto:yrudyy@prs.net.ua">yrudyy@prs.net.ua</ulink>  by Boris Yurchenko <ulink url="mailto:boris@yurchenko.pp.ua">boris@yurchenko.pp.ua</ulink> Vietnamese (Tiếng Việt) PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list.  VINADES.,JSC <ulink url="mailto:contact@vinades.vn">contact@vinades.vn</ulink> Traditional Chinese PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  liqwei <ulink url="mailto:liqwei@liqwei.com">liqwei@liqwei.com</ulink>  Peter Dave Hello &lt;/&gt;  Jason Chiang <ulink url="mailto:xcojad@gmail.com">xcojad@gmail.com</ulink> Simplified Chinese PHPMailer language file: refer to English translation for definitive list  liqwei <ulink url="mailto:liqwei@liqwei.com">liqwei@liqwei.com</ulink>  young <ulink url="mailto:masxy@foxmail.com">masxy@foxmail.com</ulink>  Teddysun <ulink url="mailto:i@teddysun.com">i@teddysun.com</ulink> PHPMailer SPL autoloader. PHP Version 5  <ulink url="https://github.com/PHPMailer/PHPMailer/">https://github.com/PHPMailer/PHPMailer/</ulink> The PHPMailer GitHub project  Marcus Bointon (Synchro/coolbru) <ulink url="mailto:phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk">phpmailer@synchromedia.co.uk</ulink>  Jim Jagielski (jimjag) <ulink url="mailto:jimjag@gmail.com">jimjag@gmail.com</ulink>  Andy Prevost (codeworxtech) <ulink url="mailto:codeworxtech@users.sourceforge.net">codeworxtech@users.sourceforge.net</ulink>  Brent R. Matzelle (original founder)  2012 - 2014 Marcus Bointon  2010 - 2012 Jim Jagielski  2004 - 2009 Andy Prevost  <ulink url="http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/lesser.html">http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/lesser.html</ulink> GNU Lesser General Public License  This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful - WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. </ref></para>
    </detaileddescription>
    <location file="/var/www/html/trabajos/hospital/views/PHPMailer/class.phpmailer.php" line="4" column="1"/>
  </compounddef>
</doxygen>
